--- Space Repair ---

A game in which the player battles time
in an effort to repair a failing space 
station.

-- gameplay --
The player controls a small astronaut and
can move them around the screen with the
WASD keys. The player can move the mouse to
control which part of the level is visible.
There are modules located all around the map
that are failing and need to be repaired.
Modules are randomly hit by asteriods, resulting
in the module's health going down a random
amount.The player can repair each module by 
moving the astronaut close to the module and 
holding the space button. Once a module reaches 
zero health, it is destoyed. The goal of the game
is to keep the modules running for as long as
possible. Once the last module is destroyed,
the game is over.

-- powerups --
There are several powerups which appear and 
upon picking up, grant the user temporary
advantages.

yellow: increased light radius
blue: increased repair speed
red: increased move speed

-- controls --
moving the player: WSAD
repairing a module: space
moving the light: mouse

-- level editor --
The game also features a level editor that allows
the user to create their own levels. The user can
right click the mouse to spawn an object where
the mouse is and can drag and hold to create 
box objects. By clicking on an object and moving
the mouse, the user can drag the object around.
Box objects can also have their size adjusted by
dragging the sides or corners of the box. Depending
on what mode the user is in, right clicking will spawn
different objects. The user can switch between modes
by pressing the relative number keys on the keyboard,
ie the 1 number key for mode 1.
modes:
1: box
2: module
3: user spawn location
4: light powerup
5: speed powerup
6: repair powerup
7: fix powerup

Additionally, the user can press the S key to save,
the D key to delete an object which they are currenly
moving, or the tab key to enable/disable object
snapping.

-- reflector tool --
The reflector tool was implemented to make creating
symetricall levels easier. With the reflector tool
expands a level on both the x and y axes and generates
objects so that the level is effecively reflected 
along these axes. This means a user can effectively
create a single corner of a level and use the 
reflector tool to generate an entire level from that
single corner.
